Who says you're only young once?
17 Again is a comedy, fantasy, drama film directed by Burr Steers.
On the brink of a midlife crisis, 30-something Mike O'Donnell wishes he could have a "do-over." And
that's exactly what he gets when he wakes up one morning to find he's 17 years old again.
With his adult mind stuck inside the body of a teenager, Mike actually has the
chance to reverse some decisions he wishes he'd never made.
But maybe they weren't so bad after all.
Mike O'Donnell, played by Zac Efron.
Scarlett O'Donnell, played by Leslie Mann.
Ned Gold, played by Thomas Lennon.
Maggie O'Donnell, played by Michelle Trachtenberg.
Alex O'Donnell, played by Sterling Knight.
Mike O'Donnell (Adult), played by Matthew Perry.
17 Again is a 2009 American teen fantasy comedy film directed
by Burr Steers and written by Jason Filardi.
It stars Zac Efron, Leslie Mann, Thomas Lennon, and Michelle Trachtenberg, with
Melora Hardin, Sterling Knight, and Matthew Perry in supporting roles.
The film follows a 37-year-old man (Perry) who becomes his
17-year-old self (Efron) after a chance accident.
The film was released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on April 17, 2009, to mixed reviews from critics, and was a
box-office success, grossing $139.5 million on a $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of high school, affectation,
time travel, fake identity, bullying.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.